Guide to the Irish Repertory Theatre Records AIA.080
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Administrative Records, 1990-2013; 3.75 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 1 oversize flat box; 203.1 Gigabytes in 57,715 computer files
  - Subseries III.E. Marketing Department Records, 1988-2016; 0.2 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 192.6 Gigabytes in 51,099 computer files
    - Marketing Archive -- 2004-2005 Season, 2001-2015 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_180)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2005-2006 Season, 2004-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_181)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2006-2007 Season, 1999-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_182)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2007-2008 Season, 1998-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_183)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2008-2009 Season, 2001-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_184)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2009-2010 Season, 1999-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_185)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2010-2011 Season, 2005-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_186)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2011-2012 Season, 2009-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_187)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2012-2013 Season, 2005-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_188)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2013-2014 Season, 2010-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_189)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2014-2015 Season, 2002-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_190)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2015-2016 Season, 2002-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_191)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2016-2017 Season, 2015-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_192)
    - Marketing Archive -- Ciaran's renovation photographs, 2014-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_193)
    - Marketing Archive -- Greenseats, 2009 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_194)
    - Marketing Archive -- Licensing, 2007-2013 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_195)
    - Marketing Archive -- Marketing contacts, 2007-2014 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_196)
    - Marketing Archive -- Marketing data, 2013-2014 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_197)
    - Marketing Archive -- Old design files, 2008-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_198)
    - Marketing Archive -- Pre-2004 files, 2006-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_199)
    - Marketing Archive -- Website files, 2004-2012 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_200)
    - Marketing data, 2015-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_201)
    - The Matchmaker, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_207)
    - Member benefit flyers, 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Membership designs, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_202)
    - New website, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_203)
    - Patron's Circle brochures, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - The Picture of Dorian Gray, 2001-2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_208)
    - Posters, 2005 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_204)
    - Prologue, 1988-2005 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Renovation signage, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_205)
    - The Shadow of a Gunman, 1999 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_209)
    - Theatre Renovation, 2010 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_210)
    - 2003 Brochure, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_167)
    - 2003-2004 season flyer (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Series IV. Financial and Legal Records, 1989-2010; 2.5 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes
  This series is arranged alphabetically by format or topic.
  This series documents legal proceedings in which the IRT was involved, financial audits, and renovation of the IRT in 1995. This series consists of paper material and includes correspondence, contracts, court documents, audits, blueprints, and the IRT's by-laws and certificate of incorporation. Legal proceedings documented in this series include suits brought by the IRT against producer Robert Macken regarding his production of video recordings of The Irish...and How They Got That Way and Fathers to Daughters, and a suit brought by Charles Nelson Reilly against producer Michael Alden regarding Save It for the Stage: The Life of Reilly. The financial materials document the production of The Irish...and How They Got That Way and its 1997-1998 tour in New York City and Boston, Massachusetts; production budgets and box office totals for other IRT productions; and annual IRT audits. Material regarding the IRT's renovation include correspondence with the architect and blueprints detailing the renovation.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Two folders in this series are protected under the attorney work-product doctrine. They was separated from the collection in March 2018 pending a decision regarding its inclusion in the collection.
  - Audits, 1990-2002 (Box 26, Folder 12-15, Box 27, Folder 1-7)
  - By-laws and certificate of incorporation, 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Fathers to Daughters, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 9-12, Box 28, Folder 1-6, Box 33, Cassette 080.0017)
  - Grant application, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Insurance claims, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - The Irish…And How They Got That Way, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 9-19)
  - Macken, Bob, 1998-2002 (Box 28, Folder 20-21, Box 29, Folder 1-12, Box 30, Folder 1-11, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    Material in box 42 is restricted.
  - 132-134 West 22nd Street, 1994-2010 (Box 31, Folder 1-2, Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Reilly, Charles Nelson -- Save It for the Stage, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 3-5)
  - State of New York Department of Law, 1990-1997 (Box 31, Folder 6-8)
- Series V. Archived Websites, September 2019-ongoing; 3 websites in 3 archived website.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of web.ovationtix.com/trs/cal/32325 and irishrep.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored.
  In 2023, YouTube URLs were changed to better capture the videos on the channel.
  Irishrep.org is the website of the Irish Repertory Theatre. The website contains information on current and past productions, script submission series, and membership programs.
  The Irish Repertory Theatre YouTube channel features videos of trailers for upcoming performances at the theater related to Irish and Irish-American works, interviews with actors and directors, gala performances, and their #TheShowMustGoOnline series created during the COVID-19 pandemic.